import { Mathquiz } from './mathquiz';

export const QUIZZES: Mathquiz[] = [
  { question: '1 + 1', answer: '2' },
  { question: '1 + 999', answer: '1000' },
  { question: '25 * 25', answer: '625' },
  { question: '4 + 1 = ?', answer: '5' },
  { question: '5 * 9', answer: '45' },
  { question: '0 * 76', answer: '0' },
  { question: '1991 * 1', answer: '1991' },
  { question: '8 + 2', answer: '10' },
  { question: '2006 + 10', answer: '2016' },
  { question: '10 + 0', answer: '10' }
];
